<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GeoMagneticKIndex</string>
    <string name="refresh">refresh data</string>
    <string name="greetingTxt">To get geo magnetic K-index data click on button below…</string>
    <string name="noRes">No response…</string>
    <string name="dateStr">Date</string>
    <string name="highStr">High latitude</string>
    <string name="midStr">Middle latitude</string>
    <string name="estStr">Estimated value</string>
    <string name="curIdxValStr">Current K-index value</string>
    <string name="g0Str">No impact</string>
    <string name="g1Str"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Power systems:</b> Weak power grid fluctuations can occur.</p>
        <p><b>Spacecraft operations:</b> Minor impact on satellite operations possible.</p>
        <p><b>Other systems:</b> Migratory animals are affected at this and higher levels;
        aurora is commonly visible at high latitudes (northern Michigan and Maine).</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="g2Str"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Power systems:</b> High-latitude power systems may experience voltage alarms,
        long-duration storms may cause transformer damage.</p>
        <p><b>Spacecraft operations:</b> Corrective actions to orientation may be required by ground
        control;possible changes in drag affect orbit predictions.</p>
        <p><b>Other systems:</b> HF radio propagation can fade at higher latitudes, and aurora has
        been seen as low as New York and Idaho (typically 55° geomagnetic lat.).</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="g3Str"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Power systems:</b> Voltage corrections may be required, false alarms triggered
        on some protection devices.</p>
        <p><b>Spacecraft operations:</b> Surface charging may occur on satellite components, drag
        may increase on low-Earth-orbit satellites, and corrections may be needed for orientation
        problems.</p>
        <p><b>Other systems:</b> Intermittent satellite navigation and low-frequency radio
        navigation problems may occur, HF radio may be intermittent, and aurora has been seen as low
        as Illinois and Oregon (typically 50° geomagnetic lat.).</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="g4Str"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Power systems:</b> Possible widespread voltage control problems and some protective
        systems will mistakenly trip out key assets from the grid.</p>
        <p><b>Spacecraft operations:</b> May experience surface charging and tracking problems,
            corrections may be needed for orientation problems.</p>
        <p><b>Other systems:</b> Induced pipeline currents affect preventive measures, HF radio
            propagation sporadic, satellite navigation degraded for hours, low-frequency radio
            navigation disrupted, and aurora has been seen as low as Alabama and northern
            California (typically 45° geomagnetic lat.).</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="g5Str"><![CDATA[
        <p><b>Power systems:</b> Widespread voltage control problems and protective system problems
        can occur, some grid systems may experience complete collapse or blackouts. Transformers
        may experience damage.</p>
        <p><b>Spacecraft operations:</b> May experience extensive surface charging, problems with
            orientation, uplink/downlink and tracking satellites.</p>
        <p><b>Other systems:</b> Pipeline currents can reach hundreds of amps, HF (high frequency)
            radio propagation may be impossible in many areas for one to two days, satellite
            navigation may be degraded for days, low-frequency radio navigation can be out for
            hours, and aurora has been seen as low as Florida and southern Texas
            (typically 40° geomagnetic lat.).</p>]]>
    </string>
    <string name="minorStr">Minor</string>
    <string name="info">info</string>
    <string name="dataProvider">Data source: www.swpc.noaa.gov</string>
    <string name="dataURL" translatable="false">
        https://services.swpc.noaa.gov/text/daily-geomagnetic-indices.txt
    </string>
    <string name="testDataURL" translatable="false">
        http://0.0.0.0/noaa-test.txt
    </string>
</resources>